so I come from nothing literally nothing
now to making 30 4050 even $100,000 in
one single day with doing probably a
couple hours of work while I'm day
trading and this has literally turned
into my new reality as crazy as that my
sound it's even crazy for me to even be
saying that right now that this is
becoming to My New Reality thanks to
trading and I've been able to do this
because I learned how to become a
profitable Trader so in this video I'm
going to be teaching you all of the
traits and Necessities you need to
become a profitable Trader and I can
guarantee you it's not about having any
special qualities coming from family
with money having any degree literally 5
and a half years ago I was working at
Dunkin Donuts making minimum wage and
pretty much just living paycheck to
paycheck and unlike other people I have
something that's very different that is
my mindset and the way how I handle
certain things un likee that's like
unlike any other people and I feel like
the way that I handle certain things
have helped me to get to the point where
I'm today I'm going to be sharing that
with you to see if I can help you get to
a position like how I am or even better
and thanks to that that's what allows me
to be consistent and it allows me to
generate numbers like these these or
even these on a daily or weekly basis
with my trading and the way of thinking
and a little bit of other stuff that I'm
going to drop is exactly what I want to
share with you inside of this video so
you guys can learn and grow on your own
these are the real traits of a
profitable Trader and the first thing is
stoic you have to be 100% stoic you
can't let any little thing take you off
you can't be emotional you have to be
bulletproof you can't let anything get
you out of your focus and get you out of
the center line that you're going to
head to success now obviously I didn't
have this major unbreakable storic
mindset that I have right now when I
started five and a half years ago in
trading this is something you develop
over time but I did have a winning
mindset I had a mindset that I'm like
you know what I know losses are part of
the game and I know I'm going to learn
them and I know I'm going to get better
but a lot of people say that but they
don't really believe that inside of them
so I don't expect you to have the same
stoic mindset that I do right now
because I'm bringing the awareness of
this toour it right now so as soon as
you realize that you need to have a
stoic mindset and I bringing this
awareness to you now you can start
developing his stoic mindset to where if
you take a loss cool I understand it's
part of the process if you win cool
that's the reason why you took a trade
you're not supposed to have any emotions
when you're trading at all and again
this is something you're going to
develop over time and you're going to
get stronger but the simplest way is
that if you fall don't look at your
hands and be like damn look how dirty
they got literally just get up and keep
doing whatever you're doing don't even
look if you got dir don't even look if
you got hurt just keep going because if
you got up that means you can still keep
going if you didn't get up well
obviously there's a problem but if you
fall and you get up don't even look back
on why you fell learn from it obviously
but don't reminisce on why you fell just
realize that you fell cuz you messed up
and then you move on and then you learn
from it don't look how dirty your hands
got just stay stoic and keep pushing
forward and that leads me to my next
point which is having 100% ownership of
what you are doing so you need to have
ownership of the good and of the bad you
can't just say yeah you know what I
bought that car cuz I made all that
money well you also have to have
ownership like you know I lost that
trade because I messed up so there's
something that I really had early on and
that was ownership whether I made the
biggest mistake with a friend whether I
did the biggest mistake with a
girlfriend I realized I was the person
making the mistake I wasn't putting the
blame on anybody else and when I lost a
trade I put the blame on myself I never
blame the market whether I got Wicked
out by news whether I got slippage I
placed the trade so it's my fault so
this is how we're currently looking on
the account right now we took the adad
buys and they weren't terrible buys but
I had explained to you guys yesterday
how we had to wait for the break and
retest we had to wait for the break and
retest of the neckline of The Head and
Shoulders now when it comes to wins I am
the one that won because I took the
trade so I have ownership for everything
that happens in my life and that is why
I accept what is going to happen whether
I lose or whether I win and this extreme
ownership is more important than you can
actually think of I can actually get 100
Traders and and I can give them the
exact same strategy literally copy paste
strategy that every single Trader they
have to check off a box before they take
a trade and they all take the same
trades and obviously they go on on their
own and the traders that don't have a
stoic mindset or don't have 100%
ownership for when they lose if they
lose they will not be successful versus
the traders that do they will be
successful because the traders that
don't have 100% ownership and aren't
stoic when the strategy has its losing
trades which is normal they're going to
blame the strategy they're going to
blame something else and then they're
not going to take ownership and they're
not going to be there again at the right
mindset to take the next trade 100%
clear and pretty much like if nothing
ever happened so I can guarantee you if
I take a 100 Traders and I let them take
the same trades and just let them run
off on their own emotions the people
that are stoic and take ownership will
be successful over the people that don't
and that leads me to my next point which
is photographic memory so this is
actually simpler than you can expect
because for trading to be successful you
don't need to be good at math you don't
need to be a genius you don't need to be
an engineer you don't need to have a
degree none of that stuff I literally
graduated high school and that's it I
didn't go to college so people think
that you need to be a mathematician to
understand trading that there's numbers
behind it there's calculations there's
not it's just photographic memory you
just need to be able to notice the
patterns that happen time and time and
time again you need to be able to see
these patterns realize that it's
happening that you've seen it in the
past and take the trade based off of
what the pattern did the last time
that's it if you see a head and
shoulders constantly happen at the top
of a resistance level you know what's
going to happen because it's been seen
hundreds of times in the past same thing
with a double bottom and much more
technical stuff but you need to have a
photographic memory because you need to
know how to react to the market based
off of how it did it last time and the
only way you could do that is if you
visually remember and if you don't
remember just take some screenshots on
your computer saves you a lot of time
and memory space if you will and don't
think you need to have some type of
talent for this photographic memory like
I didn't have it at all I came up to
trading with nothing right so you just
need to have the willingness to see
these patterns time time and time again
literally go look at the computer and
you're going to see these patterns 100
times and I can guarantee you you're
going to have photographic memory now
because it's a very simple line and it's
a very simple pattern that repeats
itself time and time again so don't
think you need to have a special talent
to have this feature of a successful
Trader and that leaves me to my next
point which is time in order for you to
be able to actually see these patterns
time and time again you have to dedicate
time into the markets but not just an
hour a day or two hours a day before you
even decide how much time you're going
to put into the market you need to
realize where you are in your journey
realistically take a step back take a
point of view of a third person fourth
person point of view where are you in
your journey because at the beginning of
the journey very very beginning you need
to put as much time possible into the
market because you have to see these
patterns time and time again the only
way for you to see these patterns happen
and for you to get this photographic
memory of what's happened it's by
putting time into the market you cannot
see these patterns patterns play out
time and time again without you sitting
in front of the market 10 12 hours a day
I did probably 12 to 15 hours a day just
looking in front of the computer for the
first 2 three months of my journey after
2 three months I realized like wow it's
the same thing that happens time and
time again so with time you will realize
that you need to dedicate less time to
the market but you can't just come into
the market with that mindset I'm like oh
I'm only going to put in an hour a day
when I'm free or I'm only going to do it
on my lunch break that's the only time
you have available fair enough but you
need to realize that the more time you
put in at the beginning the more
beneficial it will be for you because
then you will know how much time you
have to put into it in the future now
I'm probably at 30 minutes to an hour
there in front of the markets Max I
don't need to see the markets any more
time than that because again I've
obviously spent so much time in front of
the markets that I understand when I
have to be there versus when I don't
have to be there and the only way you
will realize this is by putting time
into this craft probably four or five
months down the road you don't have to
be in front of the markets During
certain sessions that don't have any
volume but the only way you will know
this is if you put the time into the
markets and my next point is money you
need to have real money to make real
results with little to no stress let me
explain let me get into detail with this
let's be honest like we're in the
financial Market we're in the business
of money so you need money to make money
you need to have a good amount of
capital so you're not always emotional
and having a highrisk approach to your
account which is pretty much prone to
get blown obviously you guys have seen
and if you haven't I turned $100 into
300K and everybody's like well I have
$100 to start you know I'm sure many
people do but that wasn't something to
show you guys that you need a little bit
of money to you know grow an account
that was something to show you that you
need the skill set but a little bit more
on that later in the video that wasn't
sustainable I turned 100 to 300K in 3
months and I blew it all in one single
week that was not sustainable at all op
that was something that I did because I
have the skill set of trading but the
moment that I entered a losing streak
since I'm riching since I'm risking so
much of the account I blew it like that
in one single week three months worth of
work went down the drain so you need to
have real money in order to make Real
Results consistently what I did turning
100 to 300K is not sustainable at all it
is literally something that you can do
if you have the right skill set as a
challenge or as something to perfect
your craft but you can't live off of
something like that you can't like you
can't pay bills off of flipping an
account not at all it's something that
you can just do on your side time or
something you can just challenge
yourself to realistically so you need to
have money in order to make money in
this industry whether you have personal
Capital whether you seek investing or
you go get funded getting funded is the
simplest route and is the reason why I
am here today there's many funding
companies out there that have evaluation
process you guys know Rocka 21 has the
easiest one-step evaluation and the
easiest twostep evaluation ation process
with as little as 100 bucks you can get
access to a 5k account which you have
90% profits SP on you literally don't
have to put $5,000 of your own money you
put a 100 bucks you pass a challenge and
then you get your own account so much
easier but in order for you to make
money in this business you have to have
some type of money to make consistent
results yes you can flip an account you
can turn 100 to whatever you want but
it's not sustainable you guys can use me
as an example I had six figures in my
account and I blew it in the matter of
four to 5 days due to the high risk that
I was doing in order to scale the
account to the point that I was in next
is patience so yes everybody hears the
word patience you need to be patient you
have to wait but it's the simple plain
truth there's no way around it same way
if you want to go to the gym and you
want to get abs you got to be patient
you have to go every single week and you
have to hit the crunches I know it sucks
it's annoying but over 6 months you will
have AB but you got to be patient you
can't expect to have abs the first week
you go in the same thing with trading
just because it's your first week
trading and you've seen a thousand
YouTube videos or you've put in I don't
know how much time you can't expect to
have results right away you need to be
patience and not only patience with just
the craft and the journey as a whole I
mean patience even with the markets like
just because you decide today you wake
up and you want to go trade that doesn't
mean the Market's going to give you an
opportunity you have to go trade when
the market gives you an opportunity so
you have to be patient there's going to
be days where you might be 1 two three
four even five days without trading but
that's the patience part because the
market isn't giving you a good
probability trade setup and the only way
you're going to succeed is if you're
patient you cannot go to the market
whenever you want you have to be there
at the market waiting being patient
until the market gives you a trade
opportunity this is so much more
effective than you guys can even think
and not only patient before you take the
trade but patient when you enter the
trade so if you waited 2 three days for
a trade set up to a line for you to take
it that it meets your strategy why
should it hit your takeprofit within 30
seconds of you taking the trade you have
to set and forget that's why I came up
with the set and forget strategy so you
literally let the trade go to your take
profit let it take its time because if
you waited two days for it to line up
you better wait two days for it to heit
your take profit so you have to be
patient not only with the craft not only
with trading but with the actual trades
themselves you need to let the trades
ride because if you're trading with the
trend you're going to succeed but that's
a whole other topic within itself
patience is key so now you have the main
traits to become a profitable Trader but
now don't think that just now once
you're a profitable Trader you're
Superman don't think you can never lose
lose that badge you can lose that as
quick as you got it because Traders once
they get that profitable Trader badge oh
I got a pay out or I got funded they
think that they're set for life not at
all tables can turn as fast as you got
there to become profitable because
Traders get overconfident Traders get
greedy Traders think that they're
literally on the king of the world
because they simply think that now that
they're a profitable Trader they're
going to make money forever and that is
not the case at all the markets will
humble you so you need to always be
humbler than you can ever expect because
your skill set depends on how you are
with your mindset you can have the most
bulletproof strategy but if you don't
have the right mindset to execute that
strategy it goes out the window it
literally does not matter and that's why
I am being so serious about this topic
you need to humble yourself as a Trader
because as fast as you get that
profitable Trader badge is as fast as
you can lose it because Traders out here
think that once you crack the code it's
cracked for life and that is not the
case at all we are always reacting to
what the market gives us and the market
is in constant change if we want to be
here 20 30 40 Years of trading you think
the market is going to always stay the
same not at all that's why you have to
have a respect for the market every
single day you come to it don't ever
think you're better than the market
because the market is literally giving
you the opportunity to execute it so
don't think you cracked it and don't
think you know what you're going to do
and this is such key to Traders because
I've seen this happen multiple times
Traders get multiple payouts and then
they think on they're on the king of the
world and after the third payout they
blow their account and they're 3 months
without being able to pass a challenge
because they forgot the mindset they had
at the beginning of that cuz now they
think they turned into a new person so
make sure you guys keep that in mind and
last but not least you need a strategy
plain and simple this is as simple as
it's going to get without a strategy you
will not succeed now do not go out here
and try to make your own strategy when
people say oh I'm trying to make my own
strategy or I made my own I'm like I
know it doesn't [__] work I just know
it doesn't work because the market is
changing so much and Traders that base
their strategy based off of back testing
I personally think it it's never going
to work I think it's set for failure
because you're basing your strategy off
of previous data and no emotion you need
to base your strategy off of real live
markets and live emotion anybody can go
and click the bar replay and go back and
draw a couple of lines but you go back
to two years and you see two years worth
of price in about about 5 minutes are
you going to have enough patience to
have two years to become profitable well
that's how long it's going to take you
to become profitable if you hit it every
single day but you will not be
profitable just by going back and back
testing and thinking now you have a
profitable strategy because you tested
it in the back testing stage not at all
you need to have a strategy that works
now that there's people that are using
it right now and making money with it
right now that's why I always recommend
my set and forget strategy but not only
that you have to stick to it you can't
just get it and think it's Plug and Play
not at all once you plug it now you
start playing with it and then you need
to learn how to adapt to that strategy
as a person because this strategy has
been made to Perfection but you need to
learn how to now you get used to
applying this strategy day in and day
out because I could guarantee you a
Trader that tries to make his own
strategy it's not going to work and he's
going to end up hating trading trading
is not supposed to be a hate
relationship it's I mean obviously it's
a LoveHate relationship at times because
price goes up price goes down but I I
love it you know what I mean it gives me
a great lifestyle and it could give
anybody a great lifestyle because at the
end goal is if you respect the market
and you respect yourself and you respect
the strategy you're the money's going to
come in by itself it's literally just
going to get dropped into your bank
account and the most important key out
of everything that I'm about to say
right now is that you need to stay true
to every single one of these things
imagine all of this like an engine of a
car the engine of a car can't work if
one of the spark plugs is missing or if
one of the cables is cut everything else
can be perfect car can have a brand new
engine transmission gas oil uh intake it
can have everything perfect but if it
has one cable that isn't connected the
car simply won't start or it can turn on
but it won't stay on so in order for you
to run this engine this machine of
trading everything needs to work to
Perfection you can't not have one yes
and one no it simply won't work or it'll
work for a little bit but then it'll end
up turning off or once you turn it off
once you stop trading for a week and
then you come back it won't work same
thing as if a car is messed up you do a
little quick fix it'll work for a week
but when you don't use it for a day it
won't turn back on or whenever Drive the
same so this engine this machine you
have to stay consistent and stay true to
every single one of these points and if
you follow all these tips you're going
to have so much more advantage to your
trading than I had when I started
trading nobody made a video like this
when I started trading and my Traders
now my students that they use my set F
strategy not only with the stuff that I
tell you but I got on a call with them
every single week and I you know show
them the pairs that I'm trading they
literally making anywhere from a th000
to ,000 $500 a week using my set and
forget strategy literally the set and
forget strategy that is the technical
analysis of my trading along with the
psychology series the private Discord
and the weekly calls that I do with them
these Traders are generating numbers
like I never did when I started trading
so if you want to know what set and
forget actually is and what the set and
forget strategy consists of just click
the link in the description below I have
a video for you there that explains
everything in so much detail because
it's crazy that my students are making
anywhere from a th000 to ,500 $22,000 a
week in the first 3 months of beginning
Trader using my set and forget strategy
so if you want to know more about that
hit the link in the description below I
hope you guys found this video valuable
make sure to hit that like And subscribe
button and I will see you guys in the
next video take it easy guys